As the New Morning Water sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua is being ministered
in the name of Jesus Christ during The SCOAN Sunday live service,
God's mighty power is clearly demonstrated
as the demons in the people are exposed and react against their will.
Watch how the New Morning Water is used to set this man free from his bondage.
This is the glory of God!
Voice out - who are you?
Who are you, demon?
I am the devil.
Ok. How many of you are in this body?
Two.
Who is number two?
Queen of the coast.
Ok. As the devil, what have you done to him?
I don't want him to serve God; he was dedicated to me at birth.
He was dedicated to you?
They gave him to me!
Ok. What have you used him to do as the devil?
I want him to smoke and womanise but he has been failing me.
How do you use him to womanise?
I send women in their 40's and 50's.
How old is he?
He is 34 years old.
You send women who are older than him.
Yes.
Ok. What do you do to those women?
How do you destroy them?
I want him to sleep with them and I pay them.
As the queen of the coast, what have you done to him?
I am in his stomach. Here.
I want him to operate and look for women.
You want him to look for women? So you gave him the spirit of lust?
Yes, I send them in numbers.
Why are you embarrassing me like this? Allow me to go!
They gave him to me. I scattered his finances.
I destroyed everything. They gave him to me at birth.
I don't want him to serve Jesus! I don't like that Name; it disturbs my peace.
I don't like this place; he shouldn't have come to this place.
How did you enter him?
I entered him through fornication.
Prophet T.B. Joshua, our father in the Lord, has sent this New Morning Water
and this is the power of God!
This is the glory of God!
You are coming out of this body!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Through The New Morning Water
Come out! Come back again!
Out!
Vomit it out!
Vomit it out! Out!
Vomit it out! Every demonic power!
You queen of the coast - come out!
Out!
This is the power of God!
This is the glory of God!
You are coming out of this body!
Out!
In Jesus' name, you are free!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Where are you going?
I don't know.
You were what?
I was seated there.
Why are you here?
I don't know.
You have been delivered through the New Morning Water sent by our father in the Lord.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Good morning, Church!
My name is Ian Phiri. I am a Zambian.
I was possessed by a spirit of the devil and the queen of the coast.
This spirit used to torment me in ways that I would have an urge -
a serious urge only to sleep with women that were older than me.
How it came about: I used to play football.
I went to Mozambique because I wanted to better my life.
I went to Mozambique because I wanted things to start moving well for me
because things were so bad at that time.
When I went to Mozambique, I went to a shrine where I found a fetish priest - a witch doctor
who told me that he was going to give me power to play good football and make it in life.
It was my friend who took me there that afternoon.
When we met this witch doctor, he told me he was going to bath me in something to fortify me
so that I would be strong, play football and make it really big in life.
So that afternoon, he took me to his place
and then he started boiling water in a very big pot - a black pot.
As it was boiling, he told me to stand and not run, no matter what happens.
So I had to stand and wait.
He told me that the moment I ran out of this place, I would go mad.
So I stood and he told me to strip but it was broad daylight.
He told me to strip, that no one would see me. It was about 10 am.
That's how he got this water and when he splashed it on me,
when it came close to me, it was so very hot.
After that, he told me to go past his wife's legs like this.
When he told me to pass through his legs, I should then just go and never turn back
and go to wherever I was going.
When I came to Zambia, things became so very bad.
I always had a serious urge and I had power all over my body - even in my eyes.
Every time I looked at a woman - be it in a club - with this power, if I just looked at her once
or twice, I would just command her to follow me and the woman would follow me.
I would just be womanising, smoking and drinking all the time.
After that experience, things were so horribly bad that I couldn't even understand it.
You said you were into a football career
and then you really wanted to boost up your football career.
You went to Mozambique and entered a shrine where you were introduced to a witch doctor
who prepared a charm for you and poured it on your body.
Instantly they poured that charm on your body, could you tell us what started happening to you
and what kind of dreams were you having that manifested in the physical in your entire life?
I would be with a woman, sleeping with me.
Every time this woman slept with me, things wouldn't work out; they would be so bad.
I would then have this urge to just chase women all the time.
I would be just chasing women -
I could not hold myself until I slept with a woman.
That is what used to happen.
And you said that instantly after you were initiated in that shrine,
you were possessed with this spirit that really made you to become a womaniser.
You were also given a power in your eyes.
Tell us - what normally happened with this power in your eyes?
How did it go, as far as destroying your life entirely?
This power was like to command women.
If I went to a club to drink, even if she was there with man beside her,
I would just look at her the first time.
The second or third time, if she went to the toilet, I would follow her
and tell her, "Leave him and follow me" and that would happen.
Even if it was a married woman with a husband?
Yes, such things would happen.
Tell us how often this happened before your deliverance.
I couldn't rest. Every time I would be looking at women.
If it was not me telling them to come with me,
it would be them - the other way round. It would be just like that.
Every time you looked at them, they would not resist it.
They could not resist it.
From that time that I went to that shrine, my soccer career crumbled.
I couldn't play football anymore.
Everything was so bad.
I couldn't hold myself. Everything was so...
I started living a very reckless life.
I could not even have money in my pocket.
Everything was scattered.
Ok. Now tell us how you came to know about The SCOAN.
I came to know about The SCOAN through a pastor
who is in love with the man of God and this ministry.
He started telling me about this ministry
and how I would get my deliverance, once I came to this place.
So he started helping me in prayer.
I thank God for his life because he really tried during the time I came here.
Can you now tell us what happened last Sunday
that brought about your deliverance and testimony today.
Ok. On Sunday, I sat somewhere there.
I first wanted to leave that place because it was getting hot in here.
I couldn't hold myself.
At first, I went out and after a while, I came back and sat down somewhere there.
As she was coming close to me, I couldn't hold myself. I was shaking.
I wanted to run.
The moment she sprayed the Morning Water on me,
it was like a huge fire that came on my body.
That's when I started manifesting; I couldn't hold myself.
I felt this strength in me that I couldn't hold like a fire that was burning all over me.
Starting from the time the man of God introduced the Morning Water,
what do you say about it that brought about your preparation for the receiving?
Ok. He said, "This is the power, this is the glory of God".
That we should start meditating upon the Word of God
as it was going to be ministered to us.
When I started with it and the evangelist was coming -
she was coming from this side, going like that -
I started feeling like I wanted to leave this place.
Even before getting closer to you?
Yes, even before she got closer to me, I felt like running away from this place.
I wanted to leave this place and go.
When she was coming closer, I was drawing back.
But when she ministered to me, that is when I felt so much fire -
like it was burning from head to toe - I couldn't even hold myself.
Immediately she ministered the Morning Water on you, you felt a huge fire all over your body?
A huge fire like that; I couldn't even look at it.
I was shaking all over.
What happened eventually?
I don't know. I sat at that side but I just came to find myself here.
All the time I was coming, I didn't know what was happening.
It was just like a huge fire that was all over me; I couldn't hold myself anymore.
So after your deliverance, what can you say?
What are the changes you have seen in your body, your dreams and your entire life?
After my deliverance, I had a dream where a woman came to me.
I was driving a brand-new car.
So she asked me for the keys.
Then I told her, "I can't give you the keys because I just bought this car".
That is how I woke up from that dream.
I sleep very well. I eat very well. I'm so very peaceful.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Apart from the dream - the victory God gave to you -
what about the issue of seeing women coming to you in your dream to sleep with you?
Do you still have such dreams?
I'm not seeing women sleeping with me in the dream.
I'm no longer eating in the dream.
I don't see people stabbing me in the dream
and I don't see people chasing me in the dream.
My dream has been peaceful from the time they ministered the Morning Water
and the time the man of God touched me.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
We can see on the left-hand side of the screen of the television -
that was exactly how the brother was declared free.
After the ministration of the New Morning Water as you can see on the screen of your television,
he was completely rescued and delivered from the hands of the devil.
And today he is hale and hearty and giving his wonderful testimony,
declaring that everything has turned new in his life.
He is completely delivered.
The Bible says that once the Son of God delivers you, you are delivered indeed.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
And right now you are delivered through the medium of the Morning Water,
what is your advice to people who are eagerly waiting for similar ministration?
They should wait for their deliverance so that they become free just like I am today.
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
And we pray that as you go and make the Word of God the standard for your life,
your deliverance will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.
TT: Mel Flowers 23/07/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 12/08/2018